

CONTACT

- Mardy.man918@gmail.com
- +1 213 985 0522
- Singapore, Singapore
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in /Hardy918
- https://github.com/DarKNight918
- ttps://hardy.vercel.app

NATIONALITY

Singaporean

BIRTDH DAY

28 / 09 / 1995

LANGUAGES

English

Native / Bilingual Proficiency

French

Limited Working Proficiency

HARDY WILKINSON

Full-Stack & Blockchain Developer

I'm a full-stack engineer with 7+ years specializing in web and mobile development, learning all aspects of the language from modern & classic patterns and implement performance improvements.

For 3 years, I have already worked on many Blockchain projects, while gaining vast experience on implementing all the features NFT project might have.

My primary concern is project's success and delivering quality work.

EDUCATION

Singapore Management University 2012 - 2016

- Bachelor of Science (BS).
- · Gained extensive training.
- Academic Excellence in Computer Science and English.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior Blockchain Developer



PowerUSD, LLC - United States

Feb 2022 - Sep 2022

- Developed smart contracts for decentralized lending platform on Ethereum blockchain
- Designed efficient and optimized solutions to keep gas usage low
- Audited smart contracts for NFT tokens and sales on Polygon/Matic

React Front-End Engineer



Golden Hippo - United States

Oct 2020 - Dec 2021

- Ported the Ionic Angular sales funnel to React and GraphQL for rapid prototyping and split testing.
- Ported the underlying deprecated Ionic library to Webpack 5, speeding up local and remote builds by up to six times.
- Developed a method for flex exclusion leading to a tenfold local development speed increase in the workflow.
- Ensured quality standards through regular code reviews of contractor's codebase contributions

SKILLS

- React
- Vue.js / Angular
- PHP / Laravel
- Go
- · Python, Django
- C/C++
- MongoDB, MySQL
- GraphQL
- Blockchain (Solidity, Rust)
- NFT marketplace
- Crypto exchange

HOBBIES

- Foot Ball
- Tennis
- Coding
- Skiing
- Game

Lead Instructor



Coding Dojo - United States

Apr 2020 - Oct 2020

- Co-authored and piloted a React curriculum at the home campus and assisted in migrating the three-stack program from Angular (MEAN stack) to the MERN stack.
- Served as a core contributor to the program-wide Discord integration, creating a rapid two-click user sign-up process.
- Created a platform-specific CLI to efficiently track Zoom class attendance and push it to the program's back end.
 This tool was eventually adopted to track course participants on a broader basis.
- Integrated the GMail API for sending automated, template-driven emails to students.

Full-Stack Developer



BotB - England

Jul 2018 - Feb 2020

- Helped the company to migrate from PHP to MEAN-Stack. It resulted in increased code quality, excellent design and increased development speed.
- Helped to test and integrate best programming practices like TDD, continuous integration, and code review.

CERTIFICATES

- Front End Web Development Certificate in 2019
- IBM Blockchain Foundation for Developers by IBM on Coursera. Certificate earned in January 2020

PAST PROJECTS

https://kanon.exchange

NFT market Place

• Developed a NFT marketplace with MERN stack and solidity.

https://www.primekeeper.my

Collaborative Inclusive Ecosystem

• Used React, particles.js, Google Cloud, React-Bootstrap, ...

https://oxfordcars.co.uk

Taxi Service Platform

- Migrated this platform React to Vue.
- Used Vue, VueX, BootStrap, MySQL, Facebook API, Leaflet, ...

https://calahex.com/

Trading Platform

• Migrated with MERN stack, Solidity smart contract